celebritysmackblog.com 2012-11-24

# Privacy Policy : Celebrity Gossip Blog: Celebrity Smack!

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Like most websites, we use cookies and/or web beacons to enhance your experience, gather general visitor information, and track visits to our website. Please refer to the ‘do we use cookies?’ section below for information about cookies and how we use them.

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

• To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

• To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

• To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

• To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Terms and Conditions**

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at http://celebritysmackblog.com

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our online privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

_http://celebritysmackblog.com  
CelebritySmack@gmail.com_

______________

### Celebrity Smack displays ads from Six Apart Media on our site. Here is their Privacy Policy:

Third Party Advertiser Cookies and Web Beacons

This web site participates in Six Apart Media, a comprehensive advertising program provided by Six Apart Ltd. for publishers all across the Web.This section of our privacy policy describes how Six Apart Ltd. and the third party advertising networks and advertisers that display advertisements through Six Apart Media (collectively, “Advertisers”) collect, use, store and disclose data from visitors to this Web site.

A “cookie” is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier that is sent to your browser from a Web site’s computers and stored on your computer’s hard drive.Cookies can be used to target advertisements relevant to your interests, based on your visits to different Web sites, to provide traffic measurement and other analytics and to conduct research.

A “Web beacon” is an electronic file on a Web page that allows a Web site to count users who have visited that page, to access certain cookies and to provide auditing, research and reporting for advertisers.

When your browser requests a page that displays advertising from one of the Advertisers, the Advertiser may view, edit or set its own cookie through your browser.In addition, the Advertiser may place its own Web beacon in the page, which may be triggered by your browser’s request.

Advertiser Privacy Policies

If you would like to contact the Advertisers to learn more about their privacy policies and what options (if any) they offer to opt out of their data collection and use, please follow these links to their Web sites:

BlogAds/Pressflex

<http://web.blogads.com/Documents/privacy_policy>

SheKnows, LLC

<http://www.sheknows.com/mediakit/articles/813566/privacy-policy-1>

Some of these third party advertising networks are participants in the Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”), a cooperative of online marketing and analytics companies committed to building consumer awareness and establishing responsible business and data management practices and standards.You can learn more about **NAI and how you may “opt out” of targeted advertising delivered by NAI member ad networks[here.](http://www.networkadvertising.org/)**

Be Sociable, Share!

  *
